Guide to the Stanford University Diploma Collection
Stanford University Libraries.
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives.
Stanford University diploma collection
1894-1947
SC4-7985
Stanford University. Registrar's Office.
1 Linear feet
Collection includes the first doctor of philosophy degree awarded by the University to George Hall Ashley (Geology) in 1894. Other graduates include Richard Keith Culver, Mortimer Clifford Leventritt, Frank Branch Riley, Helen Lathrop, Harry Carlton Burbridge, Harold Wilcox Beard, and Frederick W. Frink.
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives. Stanford University Libraries. 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: speccollref@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
Collection includes the first doctor of philosophy degree awarded by the University to George Hall Ashley (Geology) in 1894. Other graduates include Richard Keith Culver, Mortimer Clifford Leventritt, Frank Branch Riley, Helen Lathrop, Harry Carlton Burbridge, Harold Wilcox Beard, and Frederick W. Frink.
Description of the Collection
Collection includes the first doctor of philosophy degree awarded by the University to George Hall Ashley (Geology) in 1894. Other graduates include Richard Keith Culver, Mortimer Clifford Leventritt, Frank Branch Riley, Helen Lathrop, Harry Carlton Burbridge, Harold Wilcox Beard, and Frederick W. Frink.
Access Terms
Ashley, Geo. H. (George Hall), b. 1866.; Culver, Richard Keith, 1873-1939; Frink, Frederick W.; Lathrop, Helen.; Leventritt, Mortimer Clifford.; Riley, Frank Branch.; Tucker, Adelaide May.
Collection Contents
- Diplomas
  - Ashley, George H., 1894 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Donald, Robert L'Amy, 1895 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Kidwell, Minna A., 1895 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Pomeroy, Thomas Henry, 1895 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Woodward, Henry Thomas, 1895 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen, Louis, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Gould, Carl Porter, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Leventritt, Mortimer Clifford, 1899 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lewis, Elizabeth B., 1899 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Tucker, Adelaide M. (BA and MA), 1899, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Tucker, Mary Francis, 1899 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Brand, Lotte E., 1900 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Dole, Charlotte, 1900 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Riley, Frank Branch, 1900 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Taber, Clara Mabel, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Wheeler, Richmond, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Lathrop, Helen, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Wheeler, Alice C., 1902 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Johnston, John Leslie (J.D. Degree), 1906 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Mills, Charlotte E., 1906 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Tarbell, George A., 1907 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Faber, Henry Clay, 1898 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Culver, Richard Keith, 1899 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Barbour, Nina, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Rohrer, Helen Fuller, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Fuller, Helen Baker, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Burbridge, Harry C., 1908, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Williams, Francis Xavier, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Pemberton, John R., 1909 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Beard, Harold W., 1910 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Storm, Hans Otto, 1920 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Thrash, Jessee Emmett, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Frink, Frederick William, 1925, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Frink, Marjorie Mae, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Anderson, Edwin Stanley, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Burt, Frank Charles, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Erickson, Martin Richard, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Empty Case (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Empty Case (Box 2, Folder 16)